DIMITRIS DANAMPASIS

PERSONAL INFORMATION

Born in Athens, 02 April 1986

email dimitris.danampasis@gmail.com

website http://dimitrisdan.github.io

phone (M) +45 30 14 09 17

address Kirkebjerg Allé 25, 2720, København

PROFILE

As a MSc student at the Technical University of Denmark, I am currently focusing on Big Data, Computer Security and Cloud Services. I seek a full-time opportunity to utilize my skills on the IT sector, mostly developed from projects throughout my working and educational experience. It is a vision to be a part of a team in order to work on cloud infrastructures, design and implement solutions for complex business problems, involving large scale data warehousing, real-time analytics and reporting solutions. Currently employed in a part-time student job at JustWeb.

WORK EXPERIENCE

2015(Oct)–
Present

Backend Engineer, JustWeb — Copenhagen

JustWeb

- · Backend engineering in Azure Cloud Services. Design and implementation of a set of resources (Web apps, Mobile Apps, Backend REST APIs, SQL Databases) in cloud infrastructure on the Express web framework of node.js.
- \cdot Backend engineering in cloud infrastructure parse.com. Cloud code development and database architecture using the Javascript SDK of Parse.
- \cdot Development of an integration platform using Rest architecture deployed in PHP and \mathtt{curl}

2013–2014 (1 year) Web Developer, Brand Universe — Copenhagen

Brand Universe

Hellenic Army

Hospital "ELPIS"

- · Front-end and Back-end development of websites using HTML, CSS, PHP, MySQL and javascript.
- · Web-banner and poster implementation in Adobe suite.
- · Video editing.
- · Newsletter design and coding.
- · Newsletter campaigns and google analytics responsible.

2012–2013 (9 months) Radar of Surface Operator, Communications

Department — Lesvos, Greece

Tracking hostile vessels, low altitude flying aircrafts and illegal immigration by operating high tech military equipment.

Sep-Dec 2010 (4 months) System Administrator, Department of

Informatics — Athens

I was sent by Computer Solutions to supervise the network of the hospital and the installed applications. Several tasks but mostly focused on network, application and database administration and hardware maintenance.

2007–2009 (2 years) Junior Developer and IT Support — Athens Computer Solutions Several tasks such as upgrade and maintenance of the web application Bank of Legal Content for the Hellenic Court of Audit. Software training and Remote

Desktop Support in Hospitals. Data-entry operator.

2006-2008

(2 years)

Class Responsible — Athens

Language School 'Lasithiotaki'' Part-time student job. Teaching English and computer basics by using software appropriate for kids(6 to 13 y.o.).

EDUCATION

2014-Present Technical University of Denmark(DTU),

Copenhagen

Master of Computer Science

Computer Security Specialization

Description: The ongoing MSc programme in Computer Science and Engineering focuses on the design and use of computing components both software and hardware to solve technical problems efficiently and

competitively.

2005-2010 Technological Educational Institute of Athens -

Department of Informatics, Greece

Bachelor of Computer Science

GPA: 6.5 · Informatics Engineer

CERTIFICATIONS

Sep-Jan 2012 NTUA Certified Java Programmer

E-Learning Seminar from the National Technical University of Athens. Six months of training on the fundamental programing.

IELTS Test 2013

(Avg. Score 7.0)

2010 Certificate of Proficiency in English

Language, University of Lancashire

COMPUTER SKILLS

Development Python, PHP, Java, HTML, CSS

Web Frameworks Django, (Twitter) Bootstrap

> **Databases** MySQL

Familiar with Linux command line, Hadoop, Mesos

Keen on Web development, Data Mining, Data Security, Cryptography

Interested in Big Data, Computer Security, Cloud architectures

Other Latex, Illustrator, Photoshop, Video editing

OTHER INFORMATION

Projects Collaboration · Apache Mesos, a Fault-Tolerant Cluster Computing

Framework

Collaboration · Health-Care Data Handling System using Apache Hadoop

EcoSystem

 $Collaboration \ \cdot \ YouPy-YouTube \ Sentiment-Analysis$

Collaboration · America Tv Series Mining, Analysis and Visualization

DB Architecture $\,\cdot\,$ Police FIR DBMS

Languages Greek · Mothertongue

English · Advanced

Interests Nature · Technology · Space · Camping

February 27, 2016